Guide to the Francis B. (Francis Butler) Loomis Papers: microfilm, 1897-1939
Department of Special Collections
- Descendants of Joseph Loomis in America and His Antecedents in the Old World, Series 8; 1 microfilm reel
Andrade, Jos Roll I Folder 7
Andrews, Avery D. Roll II Folder 11
Aquinaldo, Emilio Roll I Folder 8
The Argonaut see also Holman, A. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 10
Army Navy Journal Roll II Folder 12
Arthur, Chester A. Roll I Folder 3, Folder 6
Ashikama, Francis Roll I Folder 1
Associated Press Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 13, Folder 15
Ault, L. A. Roll I Folder 5
Bacon, Robert Roll I Folder 7 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 14
Bainbridge, William E. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 12
Baird, W. J. Roll II Folder 12
Baker, John Roll I Folder 3
Balfour, Arthur James Roll II Folder 10
Bancaria, Cia Roll I Folder 6
Bancroft, Frederick Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 17
Bank of California Roll I Folder 1
Bannerman, Francis Roll II Folder 9
Banque Nationale de Saint Dominique Roll II Folder 11
Baptista, Leopoldo Roll I Folder 5
Baracka, Shereef of Roll II Folder 9
Barin, Frederick M. Roll I Folder 1
Barnes, B. Roll II Folder 14
Barrett, John Roll I Folder 1, Folder 5, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 17
Barrows, David P. Roll I Folder 1
Barrows, Dean Roll II Folder 18
Barry, John W. Roll I Folder 2
Bartholdt, Richard Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 14
Barton, Bruce Roll II Folder 12
Baruch, B. M. Roll I Folder 4
Bas-Ironside, [?] Roll I Folder 5, Folder 8
Bayard, James A. Roll II Folder 11
Beaconsfield, Lord (Disraeli) Roll II Folder 15
Bean, Henry N. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 11
Beasley, Delilah L. Roll I Folder 1
Beaupr, A. M. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 7
Bedford, Alfred C. Roll II Folder 16
Beel, Clark Roll II Folder 10
Belden, Simeon Roll I Folder 6
Benavides, Oscar Roll II Folder 18
Bennett, James Gordon Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 16
Beranger, Malcolm Roll I Folder 2
Bertram, James Roll I Folder 3
Beveridge, Albert J. Roll I Folder 1
Biddle, Nicholas Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 18
Bijur, Nathan Roll II Folder 14
Bird, W. S. Roll I Folder 3
Bishop, J. B. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 6
Blaine, John J. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 13
Blake, Nelson M. Roll I Folder 1
Bliss, Cornelius Roll I Folder 7 Roll II Folder 13
Boardman, Mabel T. See American Red Cross Roll I Folder 1
Bobrinsky, Countess Ludmilla Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 14
Bolt Peraza, N. Roll II Folder 12
Bonte, George W. Roll I Folder 1
Borah, William E. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 15
Bordonaro, A. Roll II Folder 10
Boulton, Bliss, Dallet Roll I Folder 8
Boulton, Henry Sr. Roll I Folder 8
Boulton, Henry K. Roll I Folder 9
Bowen, Herbert W. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14 Folder 15, Folder 17, Folder 18
Breckenridge, Henry Roll II Folder 12
British Information Bureau Roll I Folder 3
Britten, Fred Roll I Folder 1
Brown, Clyde Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 9
Bryan, Charles P. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 6, Folder 8
Bryce, James Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8
Buchanan, William I. Roll I Folder 5
Bunau-Varilla, Etienne Roll I Folder 2
Bunau-Varilla, Giselle Roll I Folder 2
Bunau-Varilla, Maurice Roll I Folder 2
Bunau-Varilla, Philippe Roll I Folder 2, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 14, Folder 17
Burba, George F. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6
Burdell, W. F. Roll II Folder 11
Bureau of American Republics Roll I Folder 4
Burleson, A. S. Roll I Folder 3
Burton, Theodore E. Roll I Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17
Butler, Nicholas Murray See Carnegie Endowment for International Peace Roll I Folder 3, Folder 4 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 15, Folder 17
Cabell, James B. Roll II Folder 10
Caceres, Ramon Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9
Caja de Recaudacion Roll II Folder 11
Calhoun, W. J. Roll I Folder 3, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 15
Call, Frank Roll I Folder 7
Cambn, Jules-Martin Roll I Folder 8
Campbell, Philip Roll I Folder 6
Campillo, Agustine Ydel Roll I Folder 3
Camplin, Edgar R. Roll II Folder 14
Cararris, J. A. O. Roll II Folder 12
Carbanell, J. R. Roll II Folder 10
Caribou Oil Company Roll II Folder 12
Carnegie, Andrew Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 14
Carnegie Endowment for International Peace Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 15
Carnegie, Louise W. Roll I Folder 3
Carner, A. H. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 5, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 15, Folder 17
Carpenter, Fred W. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 17
Carr, Wilbur Roll I Folder 3, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 16
Carter, George W. Roll I Folder 3
Cassini, Count Roll I Folder 3, Folder 8
Castle, W. N. Roll I Folder 3
Castro, Casimiro Roll II Folder 11
Castro, Cipriano Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 15, Folder 17
Central Pacific Railroad Roll I Folder 4
Central Raw Silk Association of Japan Roll II Folder 9
Cervera, Pasqual Roll I Folder 8
Chadwick, F. E. Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 15
Chaffe, Adna R. Roll II Folder 18
Chandler, Harry Roll II Folder 18
Channing, J. Parke Roll I Folder 2
Chapin, F. L. Roll I Folder 3
Chapman, Charles Roll I Folder 1
Cherry, Albert Roll II Folder 9
The Chicago Herald Roll II Folder 12
The Chicago Post Roll II Folder 18
The Chicago Tribune Roll II Folder 12
Chin tung Roll I Folder 7
Choate, Joseph H. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 18
Cincinnati Enquirer Roll II Folder 9
Cincinnati Tribune Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 9
Clark, John B. Roll II Folder 11
Clarkson, J. S. Roll I Folder 3
Cleveland, Grover Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 15
Clinton, Daniel Roll I Folder 5
Cobos, Manuel J. Roll I Folder 4
Coe, F. W. Roll II Folder 10
Colbert, Jessica Roll I Folder 3
Colby, Bainbridge Roll I Folder 10
Colijn, H. Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 11
Collier, H. D. Roll I Folder 6
Colliers Weekly Magazine Roll II Folder 15
Colonial Trust Company Roll I Folder 1
Colsman, Carl Roll I Folder 3
Compagnie du Nord de l'Espagnol Roll I Folder 2
Compagnie Gnrale Transatlantique Roll I Folder 2
Company of the Central Dominican Railway Roll II Folder 11
Conant, Harry A. Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 14, Folder 18
Conant, James B. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 18
Conde, Fabricio Roll I Folder 3, Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9
Conkling, Howard Roll I Folder 3
Coolidge, Calvin Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 18
Corbin, Edythe Patterson Roll I Folder 4
Corbin, Henry C. Roll II Folder 18
Cortelyou, George B. Roll II Folder 14
Cowles, Anna Roosevelt Roll I Folder 4
Cox, James M. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6
Crane, Murray Roll I Folder 3
Creswell, H. T. Roll I Folder 4
Crichfield, George W. Roll I Folder 4
Crittenden, John J. Roll I Folder 7
Crocker, Ethel Roll I Folder 4
Crocker, Helen Roll I Folder 4
Crocker National Bank Roll I Folder 3
Crocker, Mrs. Templeton Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 10
Crocker, William H. Roll I Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 6, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 16, Folder 17
Cromwell, Nelson Roll II Folder 14, Folder 17
Cullen, Charles W. Roll II Folder 17
Cullom, Shelly M. Roll I Folder 7
Cuneo, Pietro Roll I Folder 4
Curtis, William E. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 11
Daily Mail Roll II Folder 12
The Daily News Roll I Folder 4
D. A. de Lima and Company Roll II Folder 10
Dater, John G. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 18
Davidson, James W. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 13
Davis, A. G. Roll I Folder 4
Davis, James J. Roll II Folder 16
Davis, Richard Harding Roll I Folder 6
Davison, Henry P. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 15
Davison, Kate Roll I Folder 4
Dawes, Charles G. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4 Roll II Folder 10
Dawson, T. C. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 11, Folder 16
Day, Benjamin M. Roll II Folder 18
Day, William R. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 8
Dean, Charles R. Roll II Folder 9, Folder 12
Delcass, Thophile Roll I Folder 2
Delfino, Antonio E. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9
Delima, E. Roll II Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 14
Denby, Edwin Roll I Folder 4
De Sala, Fred E. Roll I Folder 5
Deterding, Henry Roll II Folder 16
De Vault, Charles L. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 16
Dewart, William T. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 11
Dewey, George Roll I Folder 1, Folder 4 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 16
Diaz, Porfirio Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 5
Dick, Charles Roll II Folder 11
Dillingham, A. C. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 14, Folder 15
Doheny, Edward L. Roll II Folder 11
Dolge, Rudolf Roll I Folder 1, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 15, Folder 17, Folder 18
Dos Passos, John R. Roll I Folder 5
Doyle, W. T. S. Roll II Folder 12
Du Bois, James T. Roll I Folder 5
Dudley, Irving B. Roll I Folder 5, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 12
Durand, H. M. Roll I Folder 5, Folder 6
The Economist Roll I Folder 6
Edge, Walter E. Roll II Folder 16
Edmonds, P. C. Roll I Folder 6
Egan, Martin Roll I Folder 6
El Constitucional Roll II Folder 9
Elkins, Stephen B. Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 13
Ellis, Wade H. Roll I Folder 6
The Enquirer Roll I Folder 1
Espejo, Manuel de Roll II Folder 17
Esselburne, Mrs. Ellsworth Roll II Folder 16
Eversull, H. K. Roll I Folder 6
Ewers, Ezra P. Roll I Folder 8
Expanded Metal and Corrugated Bar Company Roll I Folder 6
Fairbanks, C. W. Roll I Folder 6
Fall, Allen B. Roll I Folder 6
Faris, G. W. Roll II Folder 12
Farragut, David G. Roll I Folder 4
Ferris, Scott Roll II Folder 12
Feuille, Frank Roll I Folder 2, Folder 5, Folder 6
Fieldwick, H. Roll II Folder 9
Figaro Roll I Folder 2
Firter, John W. Roll I Folder 6
Fish, Stuyvesant Roll II Folder 10
Foch, Ferdinand Roll I Folder 2
Foord, John Roll I Folder 6
Foraker, Joseph B. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 18
Foster, John W. Roll I Folder 8
Foster, Rudolph Roll I Folder 6
Franz Joseph, Emperor of Austria-Hungary Roll II Folder 12
Frear, James Roll I Folder 6
Freiberg, Morris Roll I Folder 5
Frelinghuyser, Fred Roll I Folder 3
Frick, H. C. Roll I Folder 6
Frieberg, Maurice J. Roll I Folder 6
Frost, Louis Roll I Folder 8
Frost, Mrs. Louis Roll II Folder 9
Fullerton, W. Norton Roll I Folder 2
Fushimi, His Imperial Highness of Japan Roll II Folder 10
Glvan, de J. Roll II Folder 9
Galaves, Felix Roll I Folder 5
Gardener, Frank S. Roll II Folder 10, Folder 11
Garfield, James Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 13
Garibaldi, Giuseppe Roll I Folder 4
Gary, Elbert H. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 18
Geiger, Alfred H. Roll II Folder 11
Geneva Convention of 1864 Roll I Folder 1
Gibson, Harvey Roll I Folder 6
Gibson, Hugh Roll II Folder 16
Gil Borges, [?] Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 18
Gillett, J. Roll I Folder 6
Glennon, Archbishop Roll I Folder 4
Globe-Wernicke Company Roll II Folder 18
Goebel, Julius Roll I Folder 1
Golden Gate International Exposition Roll I Folder 8
Goldschmidt, Louis Roll I Folder 1, Folder 5, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 9
Gomez, Eustaquio Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 15, Folder 18
Gomez, Juan Vicente Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 15?, Folder 18?
Gorjao, Manoel Roll I Folder 8
Graham, William H. Roll I Folder 4
Gran Ferrocarril de Venezuela Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 15
Grant-Duff, A. C. Roll I Folder 6
Grant, Ulysses S. Roll II Folder 9
Graves, H. A. Roll I Folder 5
The Great Adventure of Panama Bunau-Varilla Roll I Folder 2
Greene, Francis V. Roll II Folder 11
Greene, Roger S. Roll I Folder 6
Gregory, Thomas W. Roll II Folder 12
Grew, Joseph Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 16
Grey, Edward Roll II Folder 12
Griscom, Lloyd C. Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 17
Grizzley Bear Magazine Roll I Folder 1
Grn, Niels Roll II Folder 13
Grosscup, Peter S. Roll I Folder 6
Groves, R. L. Roll I Folder 8
Guarantee Trust Company Roll I Folder 3
Guayana Gold Mining and Exploration Company Roll II Folder 9, Folder 17
Guggenheim, (Daniel or Meyer) Roll II Folder 16
Gulf Oil Company Roll I Folder 5
Gummere, Samuel R. Roll II Folder 9
Guy, Harvey H. Roll I Folder 6
Hadley, Elliot Roll II Folder 13
Haggard, W. Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 9
Hague, Treaty of Roll I Folder 8
Halstead, Murat Roll II Folder 9
Hammond, John Hays Roll I Folder 6
Handy, F. W. Roll II Folder 9
Hanna, Edward, Archbishop of San Francisco Roll I Folder 8
Hanna, Marcus Roll I Folder 3, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16, Folder 18
Hanna, Philip Roll I Folder 7
Harding, Chester Roll I Folder 7
Harding, Warren G. Roll I Folder 6, Folder 7
Harper's Monthly Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12
Harper's Weekly Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 12
Harriman, Edward H. Roll II Folder 15
Harris, John Roll I Folder 4
Harrison, Benjamin Roll I Folder 7
Harrison, Francis B. Roll I Folder 7
Harrison, Leland Roll I Folder 5
Harrison, William H. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 15
Hartar, Amanda Roll II Folder 16
Hartar, Elizabeth Roll II Folder 16
Harte van Jeckenburg, [?] Roll II Folder 11
Haskell, Henry S. See Carnegie Endowment for International Peace Roll I Folder 3
Havana Post Roll II Folder 17
Haven, Joseph E. Roll I Folder 7
Hawk and Wetherbee Roll I Folder 4
Hawley, John M. Roll I Folder 7
Hay--Bunau-Varilla Treaty Roll I Folder 2
Hay, Clara S. [Mrs. John] Roll I Folder 7
Hay--Herran, Treaty of Roll I Folder 2
Hay, John Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18
Hay--Pauncefote, Treaty Roll I Folder 2
Hays, William Roll I Folder 6, Folder 8
Hearst Publications Roll I Folder 2 Roll II Folder 12
Hearst, William R. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 17
Heistand, H. O. S. Roll I Folder 8
Hemphill, J. M. Roll I Folder 8
Henckel, F. C. Roll I Folder 3
Henderson, Thomas J. Roll I Folder 6
Hengelmller van Hengervar, Louis Roll III Folder 1
Henriquez y Caravajal, [?] Roll II Folder 11
Henry, Charles L. Roll II Folder 12
Hepburn Law Roll I Folder 6
Herbert, Michael Roll II Folder 12
Herran, Toms Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 17
Herrick, Myron T. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 6, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16, Folder 18
Heureaux, Ulises Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13
Hill, David J. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 10
Hill, John T. Roll II Folder 14
Hill, William C. Roll II Folder 10
Hirst, F. W. Roll I Folder 6
History of the Panama Canal in Lapidary Style Roll I Folder 2
Hitchcock, William Roll II Folder 18
Hitler, Adolph Roll I Folder 2
Hitt, Robert R. Roll I Folder 8
H. L. Bolton and Company Roll I Folder 1
Hoar, George F. Roll I Folder 6
Hollis, Stanley W. Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 16
Hollister, William Roll I Folder 4
Holls, F. W. Roll I Folder 8
Holman, Alfred see The Argonaut Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 14, Folder 17
Holmes, E. Burton Roll I Folder 8
Holmes, Oliver W. Roll II Folder 18
Holt, Hamilton Roll II Folder 9
Hoor Press Company Roll II Folder 12
Hoover, Herbert Roll I Folder 2, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 15, Folder 16
Horacistas Roll I Folder 5
Houghton, A. B. Roll I Folder 8
Howe, Julia W. Roll I Folder 1
Huerta, Victoriano Roll II Folder 11
Huffer, Herman O. Roll II Folder 16
Hughes, Charles E. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 18
Hull, Cordell Roll I Folder 8
Humphrey, Charles B. Roll I Folder 8
Hunebelle, Jules Roll I Folder 2
Hunt, [?] Roll I Folder 4
Huntey, William Roll I Folder 3
Huntington, Collis P. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 14
Hurst, Carl Bailey Roll I Folder 5, Folder 7, Folder 8
Hutchinson, Norman Roll I Folder 5, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9
Ibn Saud, [?] Roll II Folder 16
Illustration Roll I Folder 2
The Independent Roll I Folder 8
Ingalls, M. E. Roll I Folder 5
Inglares, Thomas Roll I Folder 4
Inner Harbor - Richmond, California Roll I Folder 6
International Peace Congress Roll II Folder 10
International Red Cross Roll I Folder 1
International Tribunal at The Hague Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3
Irish College Roll I Folder 4
Ishii, Kikujiro Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 9
James Stewart and Company Roll I Folder 6
Japan Society of America Roll I Folder 3, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 9
Jaurett, A. F. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 4, Folder 6, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 16, Folder 17
Jay, N. D. Roll I Folder 4
Jimnez, Juan I. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13
Joffr, Joseph-Jacques-Cesaire Roll I Folder 2
John Paul Jones Mission Roll I Folder 2 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 13, Folder 14
Johnson, E. B. Roll II Folder 9
Johnson, Henry U. Roll II Folder 12
Johnson, Hiram Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 17
Johnson, James Roll II Folder 10
Jordan, David Starr Roll II Folder 17
Joubert, Emilio C. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9
Jusserand, Jean Jules Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 9
Kahn, Julius Roll II Folder 9, Folder 12
Kahn, Lazard Roll II Folder 9
Kaneko, Kenfuro Roll I Folder 6
Karrasch, F. Roll II Folder 12
Katsura, Taro Roll II Folder 15
Kean, Hamilton F. Roll I Folder 1
Keesling, Francis V. Sr. Roll II Folder 11
Keifer, J. Warren Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 9
Kellogg, Frank B. Roll II Folder 9, Folder 11, Folder 16
Kengan, Henry Roll I Folder 3
Kenyon, William S. Roll II Folder 9
Kerens, Richard C. Roll II Folder 9
Kingsbury, S. A. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 8
Knight, George Roll II Folder 9
Knowland, Joseph R. Roll I Folder 1
Knowles, Horace Roll II Folder 9
Knox, Frank Roll II Folder 12, Folder 15
Knox, Philander C. Roll I Folder 7 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 14
Koll, Fred Roll II Folder 10
Komura, Jutaro Roll II Folder 13, Folder 15
Kowasky, Henry T. Roll II Folder 9, Folder 14
Kra, Isthmus of Roll I Folder 2
Krupp, Gustav Roll II Folder 9
Kumakeokan, [?] Roll II Folder 9
La Esfera Roll I Folder 5
Lafean, D. F. Roll II Folder 9
La Follette, Robert M. Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 16, Folder 18
LaGuarra Harbor Corporation Roll I Folder 5
Laidlow, Robert Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9
Lake Mohonk Conference on International Arbitration Roll II Folder 9
Lali, Pierre Roll I Folder 6
La Lucha Roll II Folder 17
Lambert, Dr. [?] Roll II Folder 17
Lampton, W. J. Roll II Folder 9
Landfield, Jerome Roll II Folder 15
Landis, Charles B. Roll II Folder 12
Landon, Alfred Roll II Folder 12
Lane, Franklin K. Roll II Folder 9
Langenberg, H. F. Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10
Langerman, James Roll II Folder 9, Folder 14, Folder 18
Lansing, Robert Roll II Folder 9
la Sala, Perico Roll I Folder 4
La Salle Extension University Roll II Folder 9
Laughlin, Irwin Roll II Folder 16
Lausanne, Treaty of Roll II Folder 10
Lawrence, Benjamin Roll I Folder 4
Lawton, Henry Roll I Folder 8
Lay, Julius Roll II Folder 9
Leger, J. N. Roll I Folder 5
Legion of Honor, Decoration of Roll I Folder 2
Leimert, Walter Roll II Folder 16
Lenroot, Irvine L. Roll I Folder 6, Folder 8
Leo XIII, Pope Roll I Folder 4
Leon, A. C. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 13
Leon, Carlos Roll I Folder 1
Leopold, King of Belgium Roll II Folder 9
Lesseps, Charles de Roll I Folder 2
Lesseps, Ferdinand de Roll I Folder 2
Lewis, Randolph C. Roll II Folder 9
Libby, William H. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 16
Limantour, Jos-Yves Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3
Lincoln, Abraham Roll II Folder 9
Lippton, Eno Roll I Folder 6
Lithgow, A. W. Roll II Folder 10
Little, W. S. Roll II Folder 10
Littlepage, T. P. Roll II Folder 10
Lockwood, Edwin C. Roll II Folder 10
Lodge, Henry C. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 6, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 13, Folder 17
Loeb, William Jr. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 14
London, C. J. Roll II Folder 9
London Spectator Roll II Folder 18
London Times Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16
Long, John D. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6
Longworth, Nicholas Roll II Folder 10, Folder 14
Loomis, Charles W. Roll I Folder 7 Roll II Folder 10
Loomis, Elizabeth Mast Roll I Folder 2 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 18
Loomis, Florence I. Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 10
Loomis, Francis B. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17
Loomis, Francis B. (Jimp) Jr. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 17
Loomis, F. Kent Roll I Folder 4
Loomis, William B. Roll II Folder 18
Lpez Contreras, Eleazar Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 18
Lorca Pellrross, Arturo Roll I Folder 1
Loriquet at Panama Roll I Folder 2
Loubet, Emile Francois Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2 Roll II Folder 13
Louis, Prince of Battenberg Roll I Folder 6
Ludford, E. Roll II Folder 9
McAdoo, William G. Roll II Folder 10
McAllister, Lambert Roll I Folder 1
MacArthur, Douglas Roll II Folder 16
McCabe, Bishop Roll I Folder 8
McCall, John C. Roll II Folder 11
McCormick, Robert S. Roll II Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14
McCoy, Frank Roll II Folder 10, Folder 18
McKellar, Kenneth D. Roll I Folder 2
McKenney, F. D. Roll II Folder 10
McKinley, Abner Roll II Folder 13
McKinley, William Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 16, Folder 17
McLaughlin, M. O. Roll I Folder 6
McNab, Gavin Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 9
Machado y Morales, Gerardo Roll II Folder 18
Mack, J. Roll II Folder 9
Maddox, Samuel Roll II Folder 10
Madison, James Roll II Folder 15
Madrid a Bilbao Railroad Roll I Folder 2
Mail and Express Roll II Folder 17
Mantini, J. Edward Roll I Folder 7
Marbury, Theodore Roll II Folder 11
Marietta College Roll II Folder 10
Mason, Frank Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 16
Massingham, H. W. Roll I Folder 6
Matos, [?] Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9
Matsudaira, Tsuneo Roll I Folder 4
Mayers, Charles Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 10
Mayo, Catherine Roll II Folder 10
Medico-Legal Society Roll II Folder 10
Mellon, A. W. Roll II Folder 10
Menelik II, of Ethiopia Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 16
Mercado, Lorenzo Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 15, Folder 17
Merritt, R. F. R. Roll I Folder 5, Folder 8
Metcalf, H. V. Roll I Folder 5
Metropolitan Magazine Roll II Folder 15
Metternick, Clemens Roll II Folder 13
Meyers, Alfred Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 14
Michelena Contract Roll I Folder 4
Michelson, Albert Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 18
Miles, Nelson A. Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 10
Miller, J. I. Roll II Folder 18
Millet, Frank D. Roll II Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 14
Milloy, Jerry Roll II Folder 13
Mills, Ogden L. Roll II Folder 10, Folder 13
Miyoaka, Tsunejiro Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10
Moler, William G. Roll I Folder 6
Monroe Doctrine Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 15, Folder 17, Folder 18
The Monroe Doctrine See Dexter Perkins Roll I Folder 1
Monroe, James Roll II Folder 13, Folder 15
Montauban, E. Roll II Folder 10
Moody, W. H. Roll I Folder 7 Roll II Folder 11
Morales, Carlos Roll I Folder 5
Morales, Odoardo Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 13, Folder 16
Moran, Cardinal Roll I Folder 4
Moore, Charles A. Roll II Folder 11
Moore, John B. Roll II Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 16
Morgan, Charles P. Roll II Folder 11
Morgan, Douglas A. Roll II Folder 11
Morgan, J. Pierpoint Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2
Morris, Robert Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 17
Morse, S. F. B. Roll II Folder 11
Morton, Paul Roll II Folder 11
Mulay Ali See Shereef of Wozan Roll II Folder 9
Murray, Arthur Roll II Folder 12
Murray, C. B. Roll II Folder 11
Mussolini, Benito Roll I Folder 2
Myers, J. Roll II Folder 11
Nabucof, Joaquin Roll II Folder 11
N. A. Paquet and Company Roll II Folder 12, Folder 17
Nash, Paul Roll I Folder 4